{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "After is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["after", "of", "After", "in"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: search", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["him", "the", "search", "they"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["to", "hunters", "and", "Sometime"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: that", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["that", "wagon", "they", "a"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: and", "question": "In the following sentence identify Coordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["by", "he", "to", "and"]}, {"explanation": "Sometime is Adverb", "question": "Select appropiate Adverb from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["later", "so", "sometime", "Sometime"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: help", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (base form).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["the", "him", "the", "help"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search _____________ a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["in", "by", "that", "of"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: lion", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["few", "to", "lion", "captured"]}, {"explanation": "mouse is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the _____________ being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["wagon", "tree", "mouse", "search"]}, {"explanation": "idea is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the _____________ of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["tree", "idea", "wagon", "zoo"]}, {"explanation": "go is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["let", "go", "take", "help"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: few", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["tree", "captured", "few", "hunters"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea _____________ the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["that", "by", "of", "after"]}, {"explanation": "went is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they _____________ in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["lifted", "was", "tied", "went"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: able", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["let", "lifted", "able", "go"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: a", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["later", "a", "hunters", "and"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: went", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["went", "search", "take", "After"]}, {"explanation": "zoo is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["zoo", "wagon", "mouse", "paw"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["in", "zoo", "of", "to"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: mouse", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["let", "tickled", "mouse", "able"]}, {"explanation": "tied is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and _____________ him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["tied", "went", "lifted", "was"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: go", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (base form).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["of", "being", "go", "and"]}], "success": 1}